https://bearvault.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – BearVault®
Skip to content
instagram
BUY Buy DirectStore FinderOnline RetailersUSE Tips & TricksCare & MaintenanceFAQsEXPLORE Approval StatusProduct TestingTrailsOur StorySustainabilityBEARS Bear TestingBear SafetyAbout BearsCONNECT Contact UsProduct SupportBecome a Dealer
Search for:
BUY Buy DirectStore FinderOnline RetailersUSE Tips & TricksCare & MaintenanceFAQsEXPLORE Approval StatusProduct TestingTrailsOur StorySustainabilityBEARS Bear TestingBear SafetyAbout BearsCONNECT Contact UsProduct SupportBecome a Dealer
Search for:
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policyttwist2020-03-24T23:27:10-07:00
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for bearvault.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We only collect information that is voluntarily provided through forms on our website. We may use this information to respond to your enquiry. We do not share, sell or rent this information to anyone outside our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Contact forms
Cookies
Some portions of our website may use “cookies”. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Where we send your data – Security
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. We use encryption to protect information transmitted online.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by emailing your request to admin@bearvault.com, or calling us at 866.301.3442.• See what data we have about you, if any.• Change/correct any data we have about you.• Have us delete any data we have about you.• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Close product quick view×
Designed by backpackers, tested by bears. BearVault® guards your food from animals, which helps animals stay healthy
and wild.
Phone: 866.301.3442
Email: Contact Us
Legal & PoliciesPrivacy PolicyShipping & ReturnsWarrantyCalifornia Prop 65Patent
© Copyright 2020 | Bear Vault®
